JOÃO VICTOR FERREIRA PALHA

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

I have been a fullstack developer for the past 3 years, having experience in both corporate environments and as a freelance professional working on complete projects. Throughout my journey, I have collaborated with a variety of technologies and architectures to ensure optimal performance for my code.

Portfolio: https://victor-palha.com GitHub: https://github.com/Victor-Palha Linkedin: www.linkedin.com/in/joão-palha

Blog: https://victor-palha.github.io/ Phone: (+55) 091 98970-0567

TECHNOLOGIES

JAVASCRIPT | REACTJS | AWS | NODEJS |
TYPESCRIPT | GIT | SQL | DOCKER | PYTHON

EXPERIENCES

FREELANCER, BRAZIL FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

JANUARY DE 2021 - CURRENT

EXECUTIVE SUPERINTENDENT OF URBAN MOBILITY, BRAZIL

BACKEND DEVELOPER

SEPTEMBER DE 2021 - APRIL 2022

SCIENTIFIC POLICE OF THE STATE OF PARÁ,

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

APRIL DE 2022 - APRIL 2024

Coffee Delivery — Frontend Project (<u>Link</u>)

A web application built in React to create a sleek and interactive design for a fictional coffee delivery store. TypeScript and styled-components were utilized as complementary technologies to enhance the development process.

$\textbf{Medieval Tavern} - \textit{Fullstack Project } (\underline{\textbf{Link}})$

This API was built in Node.js and Express.js to provide recipes of medieval fantasy food. The API uses the MongoDB database to store the recipes. The API is hosted on Render for free. The front end was made on React.js and with Tailwind

EDUCATION

CONTACT

Faci Wyden College (2020 / 2024)

Computer Science degree.

Rocketseat (2023 / 2024)

Specialization in the JavaScript ecosystem, both in front-end and back-end development.

LANGUAGES

Portuguese English